A Thank you.
At long last, we've finally found it.
No doubt.
Yes indeed.
Fifty long days of ferocious
battles on this journey
have all come down to this.
I don't see any signs of life.
Yeah, even the windows
are barred from inside.
It sure looks abandoned.
Jotaro, I'm sure you feel it too.
This deathly atmosphere.
A devil who possesses the
life force of darkness.
I'm certain it's Dio.
He's in there alright.
I'll take care of Dio.
The conclusion of this journey
ends a long chapter of my life.
No matter how powerful he is,
I'll cut him up with my own hands.
Polnareff, it is most dangerous
to go off on your own.
Once inside, you must follow Mr.
Joestar's instructions.
Is that understood?
There's no need for you
to worry so much, Avdol.
Don't tell me that after coming all this
way, you're starting to get cold feet.
What was that?
All right, then. Let's go.
You should look after that dumb dog
instead of worrying about what I do.
Although when the time comes,
he'll probably run away.
I will not force you to come along.
This will be our biggest battle.
We will risk our lives to fight it.
I will leave you all of
the gum I have with me.
If I should survive, I will personally
take you back to your hometown in New York.
I promise you.
I don't
know.
That settles that.
Looks like Dio already knows we're here.
Let's bust him up.
Hang on be strong holly
mrs joestar i i understand
how you feel but miss holly is in a coma.
Quite frankly she can't
hear you speak therefore
you really should go and rest for a while!
You haven't had any sleep for two days.
How dare you say something like that!
When her life hangs by a thread.
Lance's sake.
Would joseph and jotaro
still half a world away?
At such a critical moment.
Who'd watch over her?
If i don't.
Jotaro.
Papa.
I believe in you.
Holly, are you awake, dear?
Holly, Holly!
Mama,
I know right now that Papa and Jotaro
are doing their best to save me.
I believe in them.
I can't believe it.
According to this, she
is still unconscious.
Impossible.
How could she possibly
speak so coherently?
I believe in you, Jotaro.
I believe.
Be strong, Holly.
Believe in him.
Believe in your son, my grandson.
To believe in him is
our role in this battle.
There is something behind us!
Oh, damn it!
It's just a rat!
Don't scare me like that!
This is it.
It is Dio's coffin.
I'm going to let the sunlight in.
We've known this man we're about to meet
since before Jotaro and I were even born.
Yes, the blood of the Joestars
knows this man all too well.
The battle we are about to begin.
No matter what the
outcome, I have no regrets.
I am here.
Because I want no regrets.
Well, how long are we
going to stare at it?
If no one else is going to
do it, then I'll open it.
Do not be so careless.
What careless did I hear
you say? You think I'm?
careless mr.
Joestar allow me to use my fire here
hey you better not ignore me Stay back!
This is... What the?
Why am I here?
Oh, how did that happen?
Abdo!
Wait, stay back!
Old man?
Jotaro, you too.
Think about this.
Think about what has just happened.
If we're not careful, we'll all die.
Dio?
Was it Dio?
That bastard, where is he?
What did he do to you?
Get away, Polnareff.
You've got to run now.
Run.
You have finally arrived.
I must congratulate you
all for your efforts.
You bastard!
So then you're... Dio.
I know Dio's secret.
His stand.
His secret is he's able to...
Do it.
Get away!
Come over here by me.
His name is Iced.
You may have heard about him from Darby.
I took him under my wing, and
he has become my right-hand man.
What did you do to Avdol?
What did you do to him?
Where is he, Dio?
You need to calm down, Polnareff.
Why are you so anxious all the time?
Are you afraid of me, Dio?
Look at him.
He obeys me without question.
Without any fear or anxiety whatsoever.
Hey, Iced. I know.
Why don't you cut your head off?
Can you understand why
he obeys me so blindly?
It is because he feels
secure about serving me.
Many have been alienated by society
because of the superior power they possess,
their stand abilities.
But by serving me,
worthless feelings like loneliness
and insecurity are gone for good.
Do you know why?
It is because I, Dio, am the
ultimate, absolute power.
A worthy man such as Eist shouldn't
be left to die in a place like this.
May you resurrect with the
blood from my veins, Eist.
Well,
now back to the four of you,
who came all the way to Egypt with some
crazed notion of killing me, no doubt.
Uh, Joseph and Jotaro?
I must give you the
punishment of absolute death.
I must end my karma
with the Jostar family.
However, Polnareff, it would be
such a waste to have to kill you.
You are an unbelievably
talented stand-user.
What do you say?
Why don't you become my servant?
You, along with that dog over there.
And if you do decide to become my servant,
both of you will have the absolute
security of never fearing death again.
Shut your mouth. What?
You must be hard of hearing!
Shut your mouth, Dio,
and answer my question!
What did you do with Avdol?
I'm asking you, where did you take him?
Why bother yourself
with such petty details?
Why don't you tell him, Iced?
Your friend Avdol is dead.
He was swallowed up by a sub-dimension my
stand created and has
disappeared without a trace.
Where Avdol has gone is
a mystery, even to me.
You bastard!
Ah, what pressure.
It is such a waste to
kill a man like yourself.
But then, so be it.
Deal with him, iced.
Shut your mouth!
Cheap!
What?
Hold the wrap!
Boy, old man, you should feel honored.
I, Dio, am going to deal
with you personally.
Did the dog run away?
It would certainly
appear that that dog has
more brains than the two of you combined.
You bastard.
Damn it.
What now?
Where did he go to?
This is crazy!
Bastard.
He absorbs everything
in his path as he moves.
This is not good.
There's nowhere around to take cover.
I'd better move.
Notice I took a chunk
out of your foot first,
so you won't be able
to scurry off anywhere.
I will have to discipline
you for foolishly
thinking you can disobey
the all-powerful Lord Dio.
Where do you want it next?
Your arm or in your gut?
Bastard!
A spray.
My sword can only cut him
when he's not invisible.
Dio, why you... No, wait!
What the...
What's wrong?
How long are you planning
to take to come up here?
You...
Just what are you attacking?
What?
When did you?
He never even moved.
Is this his stand?
Well, to tell you the truth, Joseph, there
is a little something I need from you.
To be perfectly precise, Joseph,
I need fresh blood from you.
What's that?
From the neck down, this body is that of
my long-standing enemy, Jonathan Joestar,
and it is not a comfortable fit just yet.
Among all the humans alive, Joseph, you
are the Joestar family's oldest survivor.
Do you get it?
Your blood matches Jonathan's
more closely than anyone else's.
Jotaro!
Get out!
What?
By sucking your fresh blood,
I will fully conquer this body,
and I shall put an end to this
karma with the Joestar family
that has plagued me for one
hundred long and tiresome years.
It's only me he's after.
Hurry up! Get away!
Don't give me that!
Why the hell should I run now?
It would be wise to listen to
your elders in this case, Jotaro.
Although, I have no intention
of letting you go that easily.
This isn't about speed or playing tricks.
Could this be Dio's stand? And?
The power of the world?
Well, you old fool.
You mark the end.
You're so persistent.
Oh, my God. Damn it.
My entire body.
I can't move.
It's not for very long, but you really
should thank Avdol for extending your life.
In that fleeting moment, if
he hadn't pushed you away,
you would have been swallowed
up into the sub-dimension.
He could have survived if he tried to
escape by himself and not save you.
What a complete idiot.
Did you say idiot?
It said the more foolish you
are, the younger you die.
Damn you!
Ha!
I see you can still move.
But this is the end of a line.
After I send you to hell, you'll have
a long time to regret your stupidity.
Hm?
Whoa!
Oh! Oh!
Oh!
Iggy!
You...
You came...
to my rescue.
So sorry.
I thought you'd be long gone by now.
I didn't even think of
you as part of our team.
But then you saved me.
Thanks a lot, Iggy.
You were able to avenge Avdol.
I wish I could have
done it myself, though.
Iggy, get out of here!
He's still alive!
Iggy!
You lowly, insignificant beast.
How dare you defy the will
and command of Lord Dio?
KNOW YOUR PLACE!
And as for you, die!
Yeah!!!
Are you that eager to
pledge loyalty to Dio?
Then you can do so in hell.
Twa!
Iggy...
Isn't there anything else
you can do, old fool?
The sun is about to set.
Are you ready, old man?
K-Ka-Kyoin!
Let's go.
I don't know.
Wincerom.
A l 'alma vinci, a l 'alma vinci,
a l 'alma
vinci ro.
Thank you.
God bless you.